Dawn- Martha McLeod

#66 Third Moonan Ave Malgretoute Rd, Manahambre,

Princes Town.

Tel: (868) 469-6292/ 655-1316. Email: <u>dmarthamc@outlook.com</u>

6th February, 2018

To Whom It May Concern

Subject: Job Application

Dear Sir/ Madam,

I am applying for the available position of **Customer Service Representative** within the

organization.

Over the years I have worked in various positions, including voluntary ones as you would

see in my attached CV. I view every working and volunteering opportunity as a learning

tool used in my development by challenging myself to become the best steward over the

responsibilities assigned to me. Additionally, I am always willing to learn to be more

effective in such. It is not always easy, but that's where I believe growth comes.

In closing, I do look forward to an interview with you at your convenience and hope that

you view me as a suitable candidate for hire.

Thanking you in advance.

Yours respectfully,

John McLiad

Mrs. Dawn McLeod. (Applicant)

Curriculum Vitae

Dawn-Martha McLeod

#66 Third Moonan Ave Malgretoute Rd, Manahambre, Princes Town. Contact: (868) 469-6292

Email: dmarthamc@outlook.com

Work Experience

Feb. 2014 - Current.

TFRS Tiling Fabricating and Renovation Services.

Business Partner/ Office Administrator (Part Time)

Contact: 356-5549/ 375-0727

Duties: General Administrative and Customer Service Duties, Strategic Planning/

Marketing and Payroll.

July 2015- June 2016

Revival Fire

Administrative Assistant (Voluntary)

Contact: 225-7286/726-5601

Duties: General Administrative Duties.

Dec. 2013 - Feb. 2014

LSC Tutoring

(Worked From Home)

Service Coordinator

Contact: 330-8341

Duties: Plan and Coordinate organization's events and workshops, Customer Service,

Timesheets and Payroll, Basic Graphic Designs for flyers etc. and Marketing.

2010 and 2012

Daniel Johnson Scaffolding

Point Fortin

Executive Assistant

Contact: 722-0329/ 334-1054

Duties: General administrative duties, Time sheets and Payroll including Banking Duties, Supervise workers, Customer Service, Errands for Executives, Receptionist Duties etc.

2011

Youth for Christ

Barataria

Technical/ Graphic Assistant (Studio)

Contact: 674-3931

Work Experience Continued.

2010

Anthony Henry and Associates Co. Ltd.

Chaguanas

Human Resource Coordinator

Contact: 733-0038

Duties: Assist Executives in the hiring and firing process based on the Human Resource regulations of the organization governed by Law, Timesheets, Payroll, Develop Policies and Procedures for company, Report writing, Performance Appraisals, Errands, Motivational Incentives etc.

2006-2009

Various Entry Level Jobs (Cashier, Receptionist, Voluntary services, etc.)

Qualifications

2010- 2013	Advanced Christian Training Seminars Certificate in Ministry	
2007	School of Business and Computer Science (SBC) Certificate Human Resource Managem	*
2003-2004	Youth Training and Employment Partnership Program Certificate Level 1 Hairdressing	
2000-2001	Junior Achievement of Trinidad and Tobago	Junior Achiever

Education

2006	Private Candidate	General Proficiency	
Human and S	ocial Biology	Grade III	(3)
2003-2004	Private Candidate		
Mathematics		Grade III	(3)
2002-2003	Bishops' Centenary C	College	
English A		Grade II	(2)
Food & Nutrition Grade II		(2)	

Social-Studies Grade III (3)

Dawn- Martha McLeod

Education Continued

1997-2001 Providence Girls RC Secondary School

1995-1997 St. Joseph Girls RC School

Personal Information

Date of Birth: 13th April 1985

Marital Status: Married

Gender: Female Children: 0

Reference

Ms. Savita Beharry

Purchasing Manager California Stucco Co. Ltd. #2 Harridass St Warner Vge.

Charlieville.

Contact: 671-0358/391-3706

Ms. Rosemary Mitchell

Sales Representative Caribbean Communications Network Ltd. 70-76 Pointe- A- Pierre Road San Fernando

Contact: 652-2530 ext. 2736/470-4456

Mr. Brent Pedro

Founder/ Apostle Revival Fire Apostolic Centre 73 Bay Road Junction Marabella

Contact: 225-7682